{
    "metadata": {
        "exported_at": "2025-12-17 10:15:00",
        "app_name": "Gezondheidsmeter",
        "version": "1.0"
    },
    "profile": {
        "username": "colin",
        "email": "colinpoort@hotmail.com",
        "birthdate": null,
        "gender": null,
        "created_at": "2025-11-26 09:27:57"
    },
    "health_history": [
        {
            "date": "2025-12-17",
            "submitted_at": "2025-12-17 08:11:43",
            "notes": "Low day",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question_id": 1,
                    "question": "Water",
                    "answer": "2",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 2,
                    "question": "Frisdrank",
                    "answer": "Ja",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 3,
                    "question": "Bewegen",
                    "answer": "5",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 4,
                    "question": "Slaap",
                    "answer": "5",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 5,
                    "question": "Schermtijd",
                    "answer": "Ja",
                    "score_value": null
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "date": "2025-12-16",
            "submitted_at": "2025-12-16 09:14:01",
            "notes": "High day",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question_id": 1,
                    "question": "Water",
                    "answer": "10",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 2,
                    "question": "Frisdrank",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 3,
                    "question": "Bewegen",
                    "answer": "60",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 4,
                    "question": "Slaap",
                    "answer": "8",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 5,
                    "question": "Schermtijd",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 6,
                    "question": "Drugs",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "date": "2025-12-15",
            "submitted_at": "2025-12-15 09:14:01",
            "notes": "Medium day",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question_id": 1,
                    "question": "Water",
                    "answer": "6",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 2,
                    "question": "Frisdrank",
                    "answer": "Ja",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 3,
                    "question": "Bewegen",
                    "answer": "20",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 4,
                    "question": "Slaap",
                    "answer": "6",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 5,
                    "question": "Schermtijd",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 6,
                    "question": "Drugs",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "date": "2025-12-14",
            "submitted_at": "2025-12-14 09:14:01",
            "notes": "Very High day",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question_id": 1,
                    "question": "Water",
                    "answer": "12",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 2,
                    "question": "Frisdrank",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 3,
                    "question": "Bewegen",
                    "answer": "90",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 4,
                    "question": "Slaap",
                    "answer": "8",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 5,
                    "question": "Schermtijd",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 6,
                    "question": "Drugs",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "date": "2025-12-13",
            "submitted_at": "2025-12-13 09:14:01",
            "notes": "Low day",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question_id": 1,
                    "question": "Water",
                    "answer": "1",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 2,
                    "question": "Frisdrank",
                    "answer": "Ja",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 3,
                    "question": "Bewegen",
                    "answer": "0",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 4,
                    "question": "Slaap",
                    "answer": "4",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 5,
                    "question": "Schermtijd",
                    "answer": "Ja",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 6,
                    "question": "Drugs",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "date": "2025-12-12",
            "submitted_at": "2025-12-12 09:14:01",
            "notes": "High day",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question_id": 1,
                    "question": "Water",
                    "answer": "9",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 2,
                    "question": "Frisdrank",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 3,
                    "question": "Bewegen",
                    "answer": "45",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 4,
                    "question": "Slaap",
                    "answer": "7",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 5,
                    "question": "Schermtijd",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 6,
                    "question": "Drugs",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "date": "2025-12-11",
            "submitted_at": "2025-12-11 09:14:01",
            "notes": "Average day",
            "answers": [
                {
                    "question_id": 1,
                    "question": "Water",
                    "answer": "6",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 2,
                    "question": "Frisdrank",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 3,
                    "question": "Bewegen",
                    "answer": "30",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 4,
                    "question": "Slaap",
                    "answer": "6",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 5,
                    "question": "Schermtijd",
                    "answer": "Ja",
                    "score_value": null
                },
                {
                    "question_id": 6,
                    "question": "Drugs",
                    "answer": "Nee",
                    "score_value": null
                }
            ]
        }
    ],
    "calculated_scores": []
}